[GASPS] Pervert!
Pervert! [SCREAMS]
(In Korean) Stop that!
You pervert! [WHIMPERS]
[CRIES] Oh, my god!
You! You go!
You stay away!
Just because you're a VIP,
doesn't mean you can...
touch my body!
No, no, no, no!
What are you talking about?
[SCOFFS] You don't know?
Do you have amnesia?
A while ago, you...
[CLAPPING] You're doing this!
I could feel it!
I felt it!
[HANNAH GROANS]
My purity... [CRIES]
You mean this?
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHS AWKWARDLY]
How embarrassing!
This is what I get
for overreacting.
I think someone
owes me an apology.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[STAMMERS] Sir...
(In Korean) I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm just looking for...
for my shoe.
Because you threw it in here,
remember?
We'll get you a new one.
(In Korean) Thank you.
Uh... I'll go.
[GIGGLING AWKWARDLY]
I really hate this place.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHAIRMAN SONG] (In Korean)
Just find the necklace.
It will lead you
to my daughter.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]